Karen Shearer Collection, 1935-1996, bulk 1974-1992
Indiana University Digital Library Program
- 1. Special Edition (radio program), 1975-1994
  - 1.4. Special Edition Artist Photographs, 1979-1994, 907 photographs: b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    - Lorber, Jeff, 1986, PA 3141
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000503
    - Lovesmith, Michael, circa 1985, PA 3142
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000504
    - L'Trimm, circa 1988, PA 3143
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000505
    - Lynch, 1989, PA 3144
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000506
    - M. C. Hammer, 1989
      SEE: Hammer, M. C.
    - Mack, Greg, circa 1989, PA 3145
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000507
    - Madame X, circa 1987, PA 3146
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000508
      1987 August
    - Madden, Danny, 1991, PA 3147
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000509
    - Mai Tai, circa 1985, PA 3148
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000510
    - Makeba, Miriam, 1987, PA 3149
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000511
      1988 August
    - Mangione, Chuck, 1986, PA 3150
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000512
    - Manhattans, 1986, PA 3151
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000513
    - Mantronix, 1991, PA 3152
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000514
    - Mantronix, 1990, PA 3153
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000515
    - Maria, Tania, 1990, PA 3154
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000516
    - Marsalis, Branford, 1988, PA 3155
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000517
    - Marsalis, Wynton, 1985, PA 3156
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000518
    - Masekela, Hugh, 1984 or 1985, PA 3157
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000519
    - Master Ace, 1990, PA 3158
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000520
    - Mathis, Johnny, 1990, PA 3159
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000521
    - Mathis, Johnny, 1993, PA 3160
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000522
    - Mathis, Johnny, 1989, PA 3161
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000523
    - Mathis, Johnny, 1991, PA 3162
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000524
    - Mathis, Johnny, 1985, PA 3163
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000525
    - Mathis, Johnny, 1988, PA 3164
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000526
    - Mathis, Kathy, 1987, PA 3165
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000527
    - Max, Christopher, 1989, PA 3166
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000528
    - Mayfield, Curtis
    - Mazarati, circa 1986, PA 3170
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000532
    - Maze Featuring Frankie Beverly, 1986, PA 3171
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000533
    - Maze Featuring Frankie Beverly, 1989, PA 3172
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000534
    - Maze Featuring Frankie Beverly, 1989, PA 3173
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000535
    - Maze Featuring Frankie Beverly, 1983, PA 3174
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000536
    - Maze Featuring Frankie Beverly, 1986, PA 3175
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000537
    - Maze Featuring Frankie Beverly, circa 1980s, PA 3176
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000538
    - McBroom, Durga
      SEE: Blue Pearl
    - McClain, Janice, circa 1986, PA 3177
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000539
    - McClary, Thomas, circa 1984, PA 3178
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000540
    - McElroy, Donna, 1990, PA 3179
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000541
    - McKee, Lonette, 1992, PA 3180
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000542
    - Midnight Star, 1988, PA 3181
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000543
    - Midnight Star, 1986, PA 3182
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000544
    - Midnight Star, 1983, PA 3183
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000545
    - Midnight Star, 1984, PA 3184
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000546
    - Midnight Star, 1986, PA 3185
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000547
    - Milira, circa 1990, PA 3186
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000548
    - Milira, circa 1990, PA 3187
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000549
    - Mills, Stephanie, circa 1987, PA 3188
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000550
    - Mills, Warren, circa 1985, PA 3189
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000551
    - Mingus Dynasty, 1991, PA 3190
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000552
    - Miree, Jeff
      SEE: Jazzy Jeff
    - Mission, 1986, PA 3191
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000553
    - Moore, Melba, 1987, PA 3192
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000554
    - Moore, Melba, 1986, PA 3193
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000555
    - Moore, Melba, circa 1981, PA 3194
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000556
    - Moore, Melba, 1982, PA 3195
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000557
    - Moore, Melba, 1988, PA 3196
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000558
    - Morgan, Meli'sa, 1990, PA 3197
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000559
    - Morgan, Meli'sa, 1986, PA 3198
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000560
    - Mother's Finest, 1989, PA 3199 (Box 40)
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000561
    - Movement Ex, 1990, PA 3200
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000562
    - Murdock, Shirley, 1988, PA 3201
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000563
    - Murphy, Eddie, 1989, PA 3202
      Columbia recording artist Eddie Murphy leads a jammin' session at the video shoot for his new hot single "Put Your Mouth on Me" from his second musical CBS album, SO HAPPY. Eddie is putting his mouth on the mike with some help from his friends Johnny Gill (top left) and studio background singers. Producer extraordinaire Narada Michael Walden (top left on drums) work his magic on "Put Your Mouth on Me" and Greg Gold (top right) directed the music video for Propaganda Productions.
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000564
    - Murphy, Eddie, 1989, PA 3203
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000565
    - Murphy, Eddie, 1985, PA 3204
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000566
    - Musical Youth, circa 1982, PA 3205
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000567
      1982 October
    - Myers, Alicia, circa 1984, PA 3206
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000568
    - Myleka, circa 1988, PA 3207
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000569
    - Nascimento, Mílton, 1988, PA 3208
      SEE ALSO: Brazil Classics 1
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000570
    - Nascimento, Mílton, 1994, PA 3209
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000571
    - NdegéOcello, Me'Shell, 1993, PA 3210
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000572
    - Ndugu & the Chocolate Jam Co., 1989 June, PA 3211
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000573
    - Nelson, Willie
      SEE: USA for Africa
    - Neville Brothers, undated, PA 3212
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000574
    - Neville, Aaron, circa 1991, PA 3213
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000575
    - Neville, Ivan, 1988, PA 3214
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000576
    - New Choice, 1988, PA 3215
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000577
    - New Edition, circa 1985, PA 3216
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000578
      1985 December
    - New Edition, circa 1980s, PA 3217
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000579
    - New Edition, circa 1985, PA 3218
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000580
    - New Edition, circa 1980s, PA 3219
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000581
    - New Style, 1989 September, PA 3220
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000582
    - Nice, Rich, circa 1990, PA 3221
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000583
    - Nice, Rich, circa 1990, PA 3222
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000584
    - Nicole, 1985, PA 3223
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000585
    - Norwood, circa 1987, PA 3224
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000586
    - Nu-Sounds, 1989 September, PA 3225
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000587
    - Oaktown's 3-5-7, 1989, PA 3226
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000588
    - O'Bryan, 1986, PA 3227
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000589
    - Ocean, Billy, circa 1986, PA 3228
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000590
    - Ohio Players, circa 1981, PA 3229
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000591
    - Ohio Players, circa 1981, PA 3230
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000592
    - O'Jays, 1989, PA 3231
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000593
    - O'Jays, 1987, PA 3232
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000594
    - O'Jays, circa 1978, PA 3233
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000595
    - O'Jays, circa 1980, PA 3234
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000596
    - One Cause One Effect, 1990, PA 3235
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000597
    - One Way, 1983 May, PA 3236
      SEE ALSO: Hudson, Al & One Way
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000598
    - One Way, circa 1986, PA 3237
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000599
    - One Way, 1984 March, PA 3238
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000600
      1984 March
    - One Way, 1981 September, PA 3239
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000601
      1981 September
    - O'Neal, Alexander, 1990, PA 3240
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000602
    - O'Neal, Alexander, 1993, PA 3241
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000603
    - O'Neal, Alexander, 1987, PA 3242
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000604
      1988 February
    - Osborne, Jeffrey, circa 1991, PA 3243
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000605
    - Osborne, Jeffrey, circa 1991, PA 3244
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000606
    - Osborne, Jeffrey, undated, PA 3245
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000607
    - Osborne, Jeffrey, undated, PA 3246
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000608
    - Otis, Johnny, circa 1990, PA 3247
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000609
    - Outloud, 1987, PA 3248
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000610
    - Parker, Ray, circa 1987, PA 3249
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000611
    - Parker, Ray, circa 1981, PA 3250
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000612
    - Parker, Ray, circa 1980s, PA 3251
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000613
    - Parker, Ray, circa 1983, PA 3252
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000614
    - Parker, Ray, 1987, PA 3253
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000615
    - Parker, Ray, circa 1985, PA 3254
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000616
    - Pasadenas, 1989, PA 3255
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000689
    - Pebbles, circa 1987, PA 3256
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000618
    - Pendergrass, Teddy, circa 1988, PA 3257
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000619
    - Pendergrass, Teddy, circa 1988, PA 3258
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000620
    - Pendergrass, Teddy, 1984, PA 3259
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000621
    - Pereira, Nazaré
    - Perrí, circa 1980s, PA 3260
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000622
    - Perry, Phil, 1991, PA 3261
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000623
    - Pettus, Giorge, circa 1987, PA 3262
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000624
    - Pieces of a Dream, 1988, PA 3263
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000625
    - Pieces of a Dream, 1986, PA 3264
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000626
    - Pips
    - Pointer, June, circa 1990, PA 3265
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000690
    - Pointer, June, 1986, PA 3266
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000628
    - Pointer Sisters, circa 1985, PA 3267
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000629
    - Pointer Sisters, circa 1982, PA 3268
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000630
    - Pointer Sisters, 1981, PA 3269
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000631
      1981
    - Pointer Sisters, circa 1990, PA 3270
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000632
      1991 August
    - Powell, Doc, 1987, PA 3271
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000633
    - Pretty in Pink, circa 1991, PA 3272
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000634
    - Prince, 1987, PA 3273
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000635
    - Prince, 1991, PA 3274
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000636
    - Prince, 1989, PA 3275
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000637
    - Prince, 1964, PA 3276
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000638
    - Prince, Ian
    - Princess, circa 1987, PA 3277
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000639
    - Princess & Starbreeze, circa 1987, PA 3278
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000640
    - Process & the Doo Rags, circa 1985, PA 3279
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000641
    - Public Enemy, 1988, PA 3280
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000642
    - Qwick, Fizzy, circa 1986, PA 3281
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000643
    - R.J.'s Latest Arrival, 1988, PA 3282 (Box 41)
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000644
    - Rage Against the Machine, 1992, PA 3283
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000645
    - Rahiem, Emanuel, 1991, PA 3284
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000646
    - Ranking Roger, circa 1988, PA 3285
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000647
    - Rawls, Lou, 1990, PA 3286
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000648
    - Rawls, Lou, circa 1982, PA 3287
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000649
    - Rawls, Lou, 1986, PA 3288
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000650
    - Rawls, Lou, 1989, PA 3289
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000651
    - Ray, Goodman & Brown, 1988, PA 3290
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000652
    - Ray, Goodman &Brown, circa 1980s, PA 3291
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000653
    - Ready for the World, circa 1988, PA 3292
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000654
    - Ready for the World, circa 1986, PA 3293
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000655
    - Redd, Jeff, 1990 March, PA 3294
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000656
    - Reeder, Steven Quincy, Jr.
      SEE: Esquerita
    - Reid, Junior, 1990, PA 3295
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000657
    - Reid, Junior, 1990, PA 3296
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000658
    - Richards, Keith
    - Richie, Lionel, circa 1986, PA 3297
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000659
    - Riff, 1991, PA 3298
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000660
    - Right Choice, circa 1989, PA 3299
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000661
    - Riley, Cheryl "Pepsi", 1991, PA 3300
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000662
    - Roachford, 1989, PA 3301
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000663
    - Robbins, Rockie, circa 1985, PA 3302
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000664
    - Roberts, Juliet, 1994, PA 3303
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000665
    - Roberts, Marcus, circa 1991, PA 3304
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000666
    - Robinson, Bert, circa 1987, PA 3305
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000667
    - Robinson, Bert, circa 1989, PA 3306
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000668
    - Robinson, James, 1987, PA 3307
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000669
    - Robinson, Smokey, 1991, PA 3308
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000670
    - Robinson, Smokey, circa 1990, PA 3309
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000671
    - Rock It Band
      SEE: Hancock, Herbie and the Rock It Band
    - Ronstadt, Linda
    - Ross, Diana, circa 1980s, PA 3310
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000672
    - Ross, Diana, circa 1993, PA 3311
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000673
    - Ross, Diana, 1984, PA 3312
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000674
    - Roxanne Shanté, circa 1989, PA 3313
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000675
    - Royalty, 1988, PA 3314
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000676
    - Rubin, Rick
    - Ruffin, David, 1979 September, PA 3315
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000677
      1979 September
    - Ruffin, David, 1980 July, PA 3316
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000678
      1980 July
    - Rufus, 1983, PA 3317
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000679
    - Run-D.M.C., 1980s or 1990s, PA 3318
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000680
    - Rush, Otis, circa 1994, PA 3319
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000681
    - Rushen, Patrice, 1982, PA 3320
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000682
    - Rushen, Patrice, circa 1987, PA 3321
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000683
    - Rushen, Patrice, 1980, PA 3322
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000684
      1980
    - Rushen, Patrice, 1979, PA 3323
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000685
      1979
    - Russell, Brenda, circa 1988, PA 3324
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000686
    - Sade, 1985, PA 3325
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000687
    - Safire, 1988, PA 3326
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000691
    - Safire, 1990, PA 3327
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000692
    - Sample, Joe, circa 1980s, PA 2824
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000182
    - Sample, Joe, circa 1987, PA 2826
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000184
    - Sample, Joe, circa 1983, PA 2827
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000185
    - Sample, Joe, circa 1983, PA 2827b
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000186
    - Sample, Joe, 1994, PA 3328
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000693
    - Sample, Joe, 1993, PA 3329
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000694
    - Sample, Joe, 1990, PA 3330
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000695
    - Sample, Joe, 1989, PA 3331
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000696
    - Sample, Joe and David T. Walker, circa 1986, PA 2832
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000191
    - Savuka
    - Scott-Heron, Gil, circa 1984, PA 3332
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000697
    - Sease, Marvin, circa 1991, PA 3333
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000698
    - Serious-Lee-Fine, circa 1990, PA 3334
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000699
    - S'Express, 1989, PA 3335
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000700
    - Shalamar, circa 1987, PA 3336
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000701
    - Shalamar, circa 1981, PA 3337
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000702
    - Shan, M. C., 1990, PA 3338
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000703
    - Sharp, 1989, PA 3339
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000704
    - Sherrick, 1987, PA 3340
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000705
    - Shinehead, 1988, PA 3341
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000706
    - Shinehead, 1990, PA 3342
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000707
    - Shorter, Wayne, 1985, PA 3343
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000708
    - Silk Tymes Leather, 1990, PA 3344
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000709
    - Simmons, Aleese, 1988, PA 3345
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000710
    - Singleton, Charlie, 1987, PA 3346
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000711
    - Skool Boyz, 1985, PA 3347